AUDIENCE CHEERING
- [ANNOUNCER] LOS ANGELES,
GIVE IT UP ONE
MORE TIME FOR AKON!
♪ LONELY, I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ I'M SO LONELY,
I'M MR. LONELY ♪
- YO, AKON.
- WHAT UP, D?
- YOU COMING OR WHAT, MAN?
- NAH, I GOT A LOT
ON MY MIND, MAN.
IMMA LET Y'ALL GO AHEAD, MAN.
- AIGHT.
- COME ON.
- BYE.
♪ I'M SO LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY FOR MY OWN ♪
- YO, THIS ONE HERE
GOES OUT TO ALL MY PLAYERS
OUT THERE, MAN, YOU KNOW,
THAT GOT THAT ONE GOOD GIRL.
THE ONE WHO'S ALWAYS
BEEN THERE MAN, LIKE,
TOOK ALL THE BULLSHIT,
BUT THEN ONE DAY SHE
CAN'T TAKE IT NO MORE
AND DECIDE TO LEAVE.
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ I WOKE UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND I NOTICED MY GIRL
WASN'T BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ COULDA SWORN I WAS DREAMING,
FOR HER I WAS FEENIN' ♪
♪ SO I HAD TO TAKE
A LITTLE RIDE ♪
♪ BACK TRACKING OVER
THESE FEW YEARS ♪
♪ TRYNA FIGURE OUT WHAT
I DO TO MAKE IT GO BAD ♪
♪ 'CAUSE EVER SINCE
MY GIRL LEFT ME ♪
♪ MY WHOLE LIFE CAME
CRASHING AND I'M SO ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN GIRL ♪
♪ I'M SO LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN GIRL ♪
♪ CAN'T BELIEVE I
HAD A GIRL LIKE YOU ♪
♪ AND I JUST LET YOU WALK
RIGHT OUTTA MY LIFE ♪
♪ AFTER ALL I PUT YOU THROUGH ♪
♪ YOU STILL STUCK AROUND
AND STAYED BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ WHAT REALLY HURT ME
IS I BROKE YOUR HEART ♪
♪ BABY YOU A GOOD GIRL
AND I HAD NO RIGHT ♪
♪ I REALLY WANNA
MAKE THINGS RIGHT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WITHOUT YOU IN
MY LIFE GIRL I'M SO ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN GIRL ♪
♪ I'M SO LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN BABY ♪
♪ BEEN ALL ABOUT THE WORLD
AIN'T NEVER MET A GIRL ♪
♪ THAT COULD TAKE THE THINGS
THAT YOU BEEN THROUGH ♪
♪ NEVER THOUGHT THE
DAY WOULD COME ♪
♪ WHERE YOU WOULD
GET UP AND RUN ♪
♪ AND I WOULD BE
OUT CHASING YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE AIN'T NOWHERE IN
THE GLOBE I'D RATHER BE ♪
♪ AIN'T NO ONE IN THE
GLOBE I'D RATHER SEE ♪
♪ THAN THE GIRL OF MY
DREAMS THAT MADE ME BE ♪
♪ SO HAPPY BUT NOW SO LONELY ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN, NO ♪
♪ I'M SO LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN GIRL ♪
♪ NEVER THOUGHT
THAT I'D BE ALONE ♪
♪ I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D
BE GONE THIS LONG ♪
♪ I JUST WANT YOU
TO CALL MY PHONE ♪
♪ STOP PLAYING GIRL
AND COME ON HOME ♪
♪ BABY GIRL, I DIDN'T
MEAN TO SHOUT ♪
♪ I WANT ME AND YOU
TO WORK IT OUT ♪
♪ I'D NEVER WISH TO
EVER HURT MY BABY ♪
♪ AND IT'S DRIVING ME
CRAZY 'CAUSE I'M SO ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN, NO ♪
♪ I'M SO LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ I'M MR. LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ I HAVE NOBODY ♪
♪ FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ TO CALL MY OWN GIRL ♪
♪ I AM SO LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪
♪ SO LONELY ♪
♪ LONELY ♪
♪ MR. LONELY ♪